William S. Rosecrans Papers
William S. Rosecrans Papers,
- Framed etching of General Rosecrans, Added January, 1982.
Box 23, folders 55, 67
Box 24, folders 9, 93
Box 25, folders 1, 29, 100
Box 26, folders 12, 51, 58, 77, 106
Corona, Ramon (Mention of) Box 26, folder 53
Cousin, Caesar (Letter from) Box 32, folder 9
Cousin (Caesar) & Company Interoceanic Railway (Concession) Box 32, folders 6, 8, 58
Couts, Cave (Mention of) Box 60, folder 41
Covington & Lexington Railroad Company Box 4, folder 27
Cox, Jacob D. (Letters from) Box 16, folder 98
Box 18, folder 78
Box 53, folder 116
Cox, Jacob D.(Letters to) Box 49, folders 5-6
Cox, Jacob D. (Mention to) Box 7, folder 139
Box 18, folder 44
Box 47, folder 64
Cox, Samuel S. (Letter from) Box 31, folder 39
Crawford, Samuel W. (Letters from) Box 7, folders 9, 52, 55
Box 8, folder 15
Crittenden, Thomas L. (Letters from) Box 8, folders 66A, 154
Box 53, folder 73
Crittenden, Thomas L.(Letters to) Box 52, folder 1
Crittenden, Thomas L. (Mention of) Box 8, folder 155
Box 9, folder 72
Box 38, folder 9
Crocker, Charles (Mention of) Box 20
Cullum, George W. (Letters from) Box 1, folder 77
Box 2, folder 12
Box 7, folder 10
Box 11, folder 127
Box 34, folder 123
Box 35, folders 2, 109
Box 43, folder 133
Box 80, folder 8
Cullum, George W. (Mention of) Box 59, folder 2, 37, 41, 58
Cumberland, Army of the Boxes 8-9
Box 10, folder 33
Box 11, folders 55, 65-66, 70, 95, 101
Box 12, folder 6A
Box 18, folders 71, 97, 103-104, 111, 119
Box 19, folder 2, 97
Box 21, folders 55, 60-61
Box 22, folder 39
Box 36, folders 58, 63, 82, 85, 110, 112
Box 38, folders 23, 36, 108, 112
Box 43, folders 1-40, passim
Box 47, folder 44
Box 80, folders 23-31
Box 81, folders 17, 19-20
Box 82, folders 1, 10, 23
Box 83, folder 5
Cumberland Island, Camden County, Georgia (Surveys at) Box 1, folder 32
Cumberland Road Box 1, folder 75
Curd, Thomas J. (Letters from) Box 1, folder 109
Box 2, folders 18, 21, 25-26, 41-46
Curtin, Andrew G. (Letter to) Box 46, folder 112
Curtin, Andrew G. (Mention of) Box 10, folders 21, 25
Curtis, George W. (Letters from) Box 21, folders 108, 114
Box 33, folder 27
Curtis, George W. (Letter to) Box 21, folder 108
Curtis, George W. (Mention of) Box 21, folder 64
Curtis, Samuel R. (Letters from) Box 9, folder 141
Box 10, folders 48, 51-54, 57, 67-69, 71-74, 78-80, 99, 104
Box 53, folders 55, 58, 63, 90-92
Curtis, Samuel R. (Letters to) Box 45, folders 28, 32, 47-48, 56, 123, 126-131, 133-135
Box 47, folders 3-4, 17-18
Box 49, folder 2
Box 53, folders 88-89
Curtis, Samuel R. (Mention of) Box 9, folder 146
Box 10, folder 37
Cushing, Caleb (Letter from) Box 16, folder 110
Cushing, Caleb (Letter to) Box 49, folder 6
Cushing, Caleb (Mention of) Box 14, folder 18
Box 21, folder 69
Dallas, George M. (Mention of) Box 78, folder 98
Dana, Charles A. (Letters from) Box 16, folder 141
Box 43, folders 12, 15, 18
Dana, Charles A. (Mention of) Box 9, folder 148
Box 10, folder 4
Box 37, folder 12
Box 38, folder 136
Box 59, folders 93, 96
Box 67, folder 67
Box 68, folders 6, 10
Box 76, folder 19
Dana, Charles A. (Recollections by) Box 81, folder 19
Dana, Richard Hénry, Jr. (Mention of) Box 7, folder 56
Davidson, George (1825-1911) (Letter from) Box 39, folder 10
Davies, Charles (1798-1876) (Letters from) Box 1, folder 20
Box 8, folders 6, 145
Davies, Thomas A. (Letters from) Box 6, folders 69-73, 81-82, 96-100, 115, 123-125
Box 52, folder 3
Davies, Thomas A. (Letters to) Box 44, folders 105, 115, 125, 136
Box 45, folder 1, 10
Davies, Thomas A. (Mention of) Box 7, folder 78, 104
Davis, Henry G. (Letters to) Box 52, folder 3
Davis, Henry W. (Mention of) Box 10, folder 22
Davis, Jefferson (Mention of) Box 5, folder 134A
Davis, Jefferson C. (Letters from) Box 8, folder 63
Box 53, folder 11
Box 54, folder 81
Davis, Jefferson C. (Letters to) Box 44, folders 106, 116
Box 45, folder 101
Davis, John C.B. (Letters from) Box 15, folder 28
Box 16, folders 51, 60
Davitt, Michael (His reception in San Francisco) Box 38, folders 107, 110
Dawson, Henry B. (Letter from) Box 17, folder 7
Day, David T. (Letter from) Box 43, folder 141
Day, Horace H. (Letters from) Box 23, folder 65
Box 30, folder 39
Day, Horace H.(Letters to) Box 47, folder 112
Dayton & Western Railroad Company Box 4, folder 108
Dearborn, Henry (Mention of) Box 78, folder 89
Deitzler, George W. (Letters from) Box 39, folder 96
Box 43, folder 9
Delafield, Richard (Letters from) Box 6, folder 148
Box 11, folders 6, 19
Delano, Columbus (Letters from) Box 19, folder 65
Box 21, folder 35
Delano, Columbus (Letters to) Box 50, folders 1, 2 (2 letters), 3
Delano, Columbus (Mention of) Boxes 17-18, passim
Box 20, folder 53
Box 21, folders 5, 20, 34, 41, 132
Democratic Party (Election of 1864) Box 8, folder 100
Box 10, folder 28
Box 46, folder 112
Box 76, folder 78
Democratic Party (Election of 1868) Box 12, folder 75, 95
Box 47, folder 52-53
Democratic Party (Election of 1870 in Ohio) Box 47, folders 59, 61
Box 48, folder 43
Box 53, folder 112
Box 87, folder 3
Box 88, folder 8
Democratic Party (Election of 1880 in San Francisco) Box 37, folders 97-98, 120, 126
Boxes 38-40, passim
Box 48, folders 45-79, passim
Box 54, folders 62, 65
Box 87, folders 4, 8-19
Dennison, William (Documents signed by) Box 124, folders 4-5
Dennison, William (Letters from) Box 9, folders 68, 85
Box 10, folder 161
Dennison, William (Letter to) Box 47, folder 19
Dennison, William (Mention of) Box 47, folder 64
Box 66, folder 64
Denver & Rio Grande Railroad Company Box 21, folders 43, 49, 141
Box 61, folder 70
Box 68, folder 44
Denver Pacific Railroad Company Box 15, folder 2
De Pester, John W. (1821-1907) (Letters from) Box 12, folder 141
Box 14, folders 50, 94
Box 16, folder 113
Box 23, folder 90
Box 70, folders 7, 11
De Pester, John W. (1821-1907) (Letters to) Box 49, folder 5 (5 letters)
Box 53, folder 102
De Pester, John W. (1821-1907) (Manuscript by) Box 81, folder 14
Depew, Chauncey M. (Letters from) Box 37, folder 64
Box 39, folder 65
Box 54, folder 22
Depew, Chauncey M. (Letter to) Box 48, folder 56
Depew, Chauncey M. (Mention of) Box 61, folder 22
Deshon, George (Letters from) Box 1, folders 68-70, 74, 76, 78-79, 106
Box 2, folders 30, 38, 51, 55, 57, 71, 80, 153
Box 3, folder 88
Box 4, folders 11, 40
Box 9, folder 28
Box 11, folder 51
Box 35, folder 113
Box 69, folder 127
Deshon, George (Letter to) Box 54, folder 49
Deshon, George (Mention of) Box 62, folder 2
De Smet, Pierre-Jean (Letter from) Box 3, folder 12
De Smet, Pierre-Jean (Mention of) Box 59, folders 115-116
Des Moines River (Improvement of navigation of) Box 2, folder 83
Díaz, Porfirio (Letters from) Box 27, folder 104
Box 33, folder 78
Box 43, folder 78
Díaz, Porfirio (Letters to) Box 50, folder 1
Box 51, folder 3 (2 letters)
Box 52, folder 1 (2 letters), 2
Díaz, Porfirio (Mention of) Box 2, folders 67, 69
Box 25, folder 52
Box 27, folder 107
Box 29, folder 29
Box 31, folders 31-33, 35
Box 117, folders 75-76, 109
Box 32, folder 5, 8
Box 33, folders 76-77, 135
Box 62, folder 83-84
Box 66, folder 95
Dibrell, George G. (Letter from) Box 41, folder 84
Dix, John A. (Letter from) Box 9, folder 30
Dodge, Augustus C. (Letters from) Box 2, folders 83, 93
Dodge, Augustus C. (Mention of) Box 2, folder 11
Dodge, Grenville M. (Mention of) Box 27, folder 155
Dodge, William E. (Mention of) Box 16, folder 159
Box 22, folder 106
Donaldson, James L. (Letter from) Box 9, folder 52
Doubleday, Abner (Letters from) Box 1, folders 12, 17, 24, 26, 30, 33-35, 39, 47, 57, 67, 72
Box 2, folder 28, 50A
Box 8, folder 106, 151
Doubleday, Abner(Letters to) Box 44, folder 4
Downey, John G. (Letters from) Box 14, folder 23
Box 18, folder 93
Downey, John G. (Mention of) Box 61, folder 91
Doyle, John T. (Letters from) Box 34, folders 45, 47, 49
Drown, Thomas M. (Letters from) Box 31, folders 44, 77, 127, 134
Box 117, folders 97, 125
Box 32, folder 19
Box 35, folders 1, 23, 57
Box 36, folders 64, 103
Box 37, folder 13
Drown, Thomas M.(Letters to) Box 52, folder 1
Drown, Thomas M. (Mention of) Box 36, folder 6
Drum, Richard C. (Letters from) Box 42, folder 110
Box 43, folder 40A
Drum, Richard C. (Letters to) Box 53, folder 3 (4 letters)
Duane, James C. (Mention of) Box 2, folder 4
Du Bois, Henry A. (Letters from) Box 31, folder 11
Duncan, William B. (Letter from) Box 17, folder 31
Du Pont, Lammont (Letter from) Box 36, folder 106
Box 54, folder 51
Du Pont, Lammont (Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Du Pont, Lammont (Mention of) Box 36, folders 95, 102
Du Pont, Samuel F. (Mention of) Box 2, folders 92, 94
Dyer, Elisha (Letters from) Box 16, folders 84, 124
Box 17, folders 90, 98, 102, 109, 141
Dyer, Elisha (Letters to) Box 50, folders 1-3
Dyer, Elisha (Mention of) Box 17, folder 94
Eastern Nevada Railroad Company Box 21, folder 119
Eaton, Lucian (Mention of) Box 10, folder 27
Elliott, Washington L. (Letters from) Box 9, folder 8
Box 30, folder 113
Emancipation Proclamation, September 22, 1862 Box 1, folder 135
Embargo laws of 1813-1814 (Passed and repealed by Congress) Box 78, folders 91-92, 97, 121
Este, George P. (Letter from) Box 19, folder 144
Este, George P.(Letters to) Box 49, folder 6
Box 50, folder 1
Eustis, Henry L. (Letters from) Box 1, folders 96, 110
Box 2, folder 3, 8
Evarts, William M.(Letter to) Box 15, folder 45
Ewell, Richard S. (Mention of) Box 80, folder 25
Ewing, Hugh B. (Letters from) Box 6, folder 144
Box 7, folder 139
Ewing, Hugh B. (Mention of) Box 7, folder 84
Box 59, folder 122
Ewing, Thomas (1829-1896) (Letters from) Box 5, folders 102, 105, 123, 127, 132, 155
Box 6, folders 6, 10
Box 10, folder 113
Ewing, Thomas (1829-1896) (Letter to) Box 49, folder 6
Ewing, Thomas (1829-1896) (Mention of) Box 5, folder 151
Ewing, Thomas (1829-1896) (Printed address by) Box 87, folder 1
Fair, James G. (Letter from) Box 42, folder 37
Fair, James G.(Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Fayetteville, Arkansas (Skirmish at, 1864) Box 10, folder 99
Felton, Samuel M. (Letter from) Box 26, folder 152
Fenton, Reuben E. (Letters from) Box 18, folder 140
Box 32, folder 25
Fenton, Reuben E. (Letters to) Box 47, folder 72
Box 49, folder 6
Box 50, folder 1
Fenton, Reuben E. (Mention of) Box 61, folders 17, 60
Box 67, folders 81, 83
Fernald, Charles H. (Letters from) Box 11, folder 48
Box 15, folder 107
Box 16, folder 58
Fernald, Charles H. (Letters to) Box 49, folder 6 (2 letters)
Fessenden, Samuel C. (Letter from) Box 53, folder 57
Fish, Hamilton (Letters from) Box 47, folders 55, 69
Fish, Hamilton (Letter to) Box 49, folder 6
Fish, Hamilton (Mention of) Box 14, folders 54, 62
Box 19, folders 130-133
Box 26, folder 102
Fitch, Thomas (1838-1923) (Letter from) Box 16, folder 129
Fitton, James (1805-1881) (Letter from) Box 5, folder 140
Fitzpatrick, John B. (Letters from) Box 7, folder 43
Fletcher, Thomas C. (Letter from) Box 10, folder 146
Fletcher, Thomas C. (Mention of) Box 10, folders 114, 126
Box 59, folder 122
Flood, James C. (Letter from) Box 70, folder 58
Flood, James C. (Letters to) Box 48, folders 72, 79
Box 52, folder 1
Flower, Roswell P. (Printed speech by) Box 87, folder 24
Floyd, John B. (Mention of) Box 7, folder 41
Box 59, folders 24, 27, 29
Box 66, folder 108
Box 86, folder 9
Force, Manning F. (Letter from) Box 19, folder 119
Force, Manning F.(Letter to) Box 47, folder 87
Ford, Patrick (1835-1913) (Letters from) Box 42, folder 12, 31
Fordham University Box 1, folder 81
Box 66, folders 8-27
Box 76, folders 1-6
Forrest, Nathan B. (Letters from) Box 12, folder 58
Forrest, Nathan B. (Mention of) Box 9, folder 129
Forsyth, John (1780-1841) (Mention of) Box 78, folder 98
Fort Adams, Newport, Rhode Island Box 1, folder 96
Box 2, folders 12, 121
Box 3, folders 7, 46, 65, 70, 93, 147
Fort Columbus, Governors Island, New York Box 2, folder 50A
Fort Johnson, Smithville, North Carolina Box 1, folders 24, 26, 30, 35, 39
Fort Monroe, Old Point Comfort, Virginia Box 1, folder 48
Box 58, folders 27, 35
Fort Sumter Box 2, folder 37
Fort Warren, Boston Box 1, folder 80
Foster, John Gray (Letters from) Box 12, folder 29A
Box 31, folder 52
Foster, John Gray (Mention of) Box 32, folders 59-60
Box 43, folder 133
Franklin, William Buel (Letter from) Box 42, folder 77
Fredonia (U.S. Ship) Box 2, folder 158
Freeman, Daniel (Mention of) Box 28, folder 18
Frémont, Jesse (Benton) (Letter from) Box 9, folder 91
Frémont, John C. (Letter from) Box 16, folder 63
Frémont, John C.(Letters to) Box 49, folder 6 (2 letters)
Frémont, John C. (Mention of) Box 7, folder 59
Box 16, folders 46, 55, 109
Box 17, folders 46, 92, 94
Box 18, folders 26, 42, 46, 52, 68, 75
Box 21, folder 22
Box 25, folder 139
Box 59, folders 43, 45
Box 61, folders 21, 23
Box 66, folders 56, 61, 115
Box 68, folders 4-5, 23
Box 69, folder 15
Fry, James B. (Letters from) Box 53, folder 85
Box 54, folder 64
Fry, James B. (Printed tribute to General George L. Hartsuff by) Box 30, folder 118A
Fuller, John W. (Letter from) Box 18, folder 98
Box 34, folders 79, 100
Box 43, folder 36
Fuller, John W.(Letter to) Box 48, folder 30
Gabb, William M. (Letter from) Box 14, folder 6A
Gallagher, Hugh P. (Letter from) Box 27, folder 111
Gantt, Thomas T. (Letter from) Box 10, folder 117
Garesché, Julius P. (Letters from) Box 2, folders 54A, 70, 97
Box 3, folders 71, 100
Box 4, folders 2, 12
Box 6, folders 3, 55
Box 7, folder 39
Garesché, Julius P. (Mention of) Box 8, folder 81
Box 16, folder 53
Box 36, folder 107
Box 47, folder 70
Box 59, folder 72
Garfield, James A. (Letters from) Box 8, folder 78, 148
Box 9, folders 4, 37, 44, 58, 84, 104, 116, 135, 155
Box 10, folders 5, 13, 105, 139, 157
Box 11, folders 5, 20, 30, 43, 128
Box 12, folders 47, 71
Box 16, folder 140
Box 18, folder 111
Box 20, folder 37
Box 29, folder 89
Box 32, folders 119, 145
Box 35, folder 5
Box 36, folder 82
Box 37, folders 12, 43, 46
Box 38, folder 37
Box 39, folder 126
Box 40, folder 111
Box 49, folder 2
Box 69, folders 55, 103
Garfield, James A.(Letters to) Box 46, folders 98, 101-102
Box 47, folder 21
Box 48, folder 44
Box 49, folders 2 (3 letters), 5, 6
Box 50, folders 1 (2 letters), 3
Box 52, folder 1 (3 letters)
Box 53, folders 73-75, 76A, 81, 103
Box 54, folders 53, 58
Garfield, James A. (Mention of) Box 9, folders 36, 40, 148
Box 10, folder 22
Box 20, folder 37
Box 21, folder 72
Box 32, folder 65
Boxes 38-41, passim
Box 43, folders 1-40, passim
Box 48, folders 37, 61-63, 66, 110
Box 57, folder 99
Box 59, folders 71, 74, 91A
Box 60, folder 45
Box 61, folders 21-22, 72
Box 62, folder 113A
Box 68, folder 6
Box 76, folders 63, 77
Box 81, folders 10, 16
Box 82, folder 26
Box 87, folder 19A
Gates, William (1788-1868) (Mention of) Box 3, folder 92
George, Henry (Letter from) Box 36, folder 57
Germans in California Box 21, folder 54
Getty, George W. (Letter from) Box 42, folder 98
Ghent, Treaty of, 1814 Box 78, folder 99
Gibbons, James (1834-1921) (Letter from) Box 27, folder 124
Gilmore, James R. (Letters from) Box 8, folder 61
Box 9, folders 5, 142, 148
Box 40, folders 20, 63, 87, 98, 110
Box 41, folder 19
Box 43, folder 48
Gladstone, William E.(Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Glover, Samuel T.(Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Goat Island, Newport, Rhode Island Box 2, folders 149-150
Gordon, John B. (Letter from) Box 12, folder 61
Gorgas, Josiah (Letter from) Box 1, folder 14
Gorgas, Josiah (Mention of) Box 44, folder 4
Gould, Jay (Letter to) Box 52, folder 3
Graham, William A. (Letter from) Box 12, folder 50
Grand Army of the Republic, Lincoln Post (no.1, San Francisco) Box 82, folder 5
Granger, Gordon (Letters from) Box 8, folders 67, 122
Box 10, folder 4
Box 53, folders 74-75
Box 59, folder 37
Grant, Julia (Dent) (Letter from) Box 10, folder 8
Grant, Ulysses S. (Letters from) Box 7, folders 68-68A, 74-75, 77, 83-85, 101-103, 116, 125-126, 128, 130-132, 143
Box 9, folders 113, 123, 127, 129-130, 133, 136-137, 139
Box 17, folder 114
Grant, Ulysses S. (Letters to) Box 44, folders 29-30, 34-35, 43-44, 63-67, 93- 99, 107-110, 117-118, 124, 126-130, 138-141
Box 45, folders 3-4, 12, 16-18, 21-23, 37-41, 49, 57-61, 70-72, 78-80, 89-90, 102
Box 47, folder 29
Box 49, folders 2, 5
Box 50, folder 1
Box 53, folders 25, 30
Grant, Ulysses S. (Mention of) Box 8, folders 5, 23, 103A, 119, 135
Box 9, folders 3, 19, 74, 106, 110, 148
Box 10, folders 4, 25, 92
Box 11, folders 14, 105, 127
Box 14, folders 18, 32, 42, 54, 56
Box 17, folders 139, 160
Box 19, folders 130, 135
Box 21, folder 10, 98
Box 24, folder 62
Box 29, folder 29
Box 32, folder 101
Box 34, folder 89
Box 38, folder 136
Box 40, folder 113
Box 47, folder 64
Box 48, folders 30, 67, 110-111
Box 54, folder 79
Box 59, folders 43, 50, 58, 115
Box 60, folders 6, 33
Box 62, folders 16, 120
Box 63, folder 42
Box 66, folders 62-65, 73, 100, 121
Box 67, folders 60, 65, 67, 69, 83
Box 68, folder 4, 46
Box 71, folder 69
Box 81, folders 21-22
Box 86, folders 5-6
Grant, Ulysses S. (His cabinet) Box 14, folders 24, 29
Grant, Ulysses S. (Opposition to the bill to place him on the U.S. Army retired list) Box 43, folders 44-71
Grass Valley, California (Copper mining at) Box 11, folder 23
Greeley, Horace (Letter to) Box 81, folder 11
Greeley, Horace (Mention of) Box 16, folder 20
Box 17, folders 43, 54, 70
Box 24, folders 62, 78
Box 55, folder 113
Box 60, folder 32
Box 67, folder 91
Box 68, folder 46
Box 76, folder 53
Green, Duff (Letter from) Box 12, folder 27
Greenwood, Miles(Letter to) Box 50, folder 1
Griswold, John A. (Mention of) Box 14, folder 18
Grose, William (1812-1900) (Letter from) Box 28, folder 13
Grosvenor, Thomas P. (Mention of) Box 78, folder 92
Grover, La Fayette(Letters to) Box 52, folder 3 (2 letters)
Guadalupe Hidalgo, Treaty of Box 12, folder 53
Guaymas & El Paso Railroad Company Box 61, folder 78
Gunckel, Lewis B. (Letter from) Box 17, folder 56
Guthrie, James (1792-1869) (Mention of) Box 3, folder 127
Guthrie, John J. (Letter from) Box 4, folder 8
Gwin, William M. (Letter from) Box 38, folder 118
Gwin, William M. (Mention of) Box 37, folder 83
Hager, John S. (Letter from) Box 39, folder 91
Hager, John S. (Printed speech by) Box 87, folder 5
Haight, Henry H. (Mention of) Box 17, folder 85
Hall, Joshua G. (Letter to) Box 52, folder 3
Hall, Willard P. (Document signed by) Box 124, folder 9
Hall, Willard P. (Letter from) Box 9, folder 84A
Hall, Willard P.(Letter to) Box 49, folder 2
Hall, Willard P. (Mention of) Box 59, folder 112
Halleck, Henry W. (Letters from) Box 7, folders 67, 149
Box 8, folders 27, 38, 44, 58, 79, 89, 93-97, 101-103, 103B, 109, 112, 116A, 119-120, 125, 135, 140-141
Box 9, folders 80, 96, 98, 110-111, 138, 143-144, 152, 156
Box 10, folders 3, 9, 26, 32, 34, 36-37, 40, 81-86, 89-92, 95-98
Box 49, folder 2 (10 letters)
Box 53, folders 53, 69
Halleck, Henry W. (Letters to) Box 45, folders 5, 90-92, 109, 111-112, 114-117, 121-122, 124-125, 127-128, 130, 132, 140
Box 46, folders 1, 5, 7-8, 14, 16, 28, 30, 34-51, 54-58, 60-61, 63-70, 74, 76, 137
Box 47, folders 2, 5-13, 15
Box 49 (10 letters)
Halleck, Henry W. (Mention of) Box 2, folders 82, 157, 164
Box 4, folders 15, 134A
Box 7, folder 116
Box 8, folder 113A
Box 9, folders 40, 57, 116
Box 10, folders 170, 180
Box 14, folder 36
Box 21, folder 98
Box 39, folder 112
Box 40, folder 65
Box 43, folder 54
Box 48, folder 110
Box 56, folder 46
Box 59, folders 37, 39, 44, 50, 107
Box 60, folder 75
Box 66, folder 110
Box 71, folder 46
Box 86, folder 6
Halstead, Murat (Letter from) Box 31, folder 76
Halstead, Murat (Letters to) Box 48, folders 61, 66, 74
Hamilton, Andrew J. (Mention of) Box 9, folder 3
Hamilton, Charles S. (Letters from) Box 7, folders 78-79, 89
Box 53, folders 31, 33-35, 39-44, 48, 61-62
Hamilton, Charles S. (Letters to) Box 44, folders 24, 36, 45, 69-72, 77, 115, 119-120, 136
Box 45, folder 104
Hamilton, Charles S. (Mention of) Box 8, folder 30
Hamilton, Charles S. (Printed article by) Box 81, folder 31
Hamilton, Schuyler (Letters from) Box 2, folders 61, 78
Box 8, folders 7, 32
Box 12, folders 53, 79, 139
Hamilton, Schuyler (Printed address by) Box 80, folder 3
Hampton, Wade (Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Hancock, Winfield S. (Letters from) Box 38, folder 40
Box 39, folder 7
Hancock, Winfield S.(Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Hancock, Winfield S. (Mention of) Box 21, folder 10
Box 36, folder 50
Box 37, folders 31, 38-39, passim
Box 54, folder 64
Hansen, George, Surveyor, Los Angeles (Letters from) Box 11, folder 80
Hanson, Alexander C. (Mention of) Box 78, folders 88, 90, 98
Hardie, James A. (Letters from) Box 2, folders 56B, 158, 166
Box 3, folders 59, 85, 92, 110
Box 4, folders 6, 42, 98B
Box 5, folders 134A, 148
Box 6, folder 126
Box 10, folder 14
Box 11, folder 7
Box 49, folder 2
Box 69, folder 56
Hardie, James A. (Mention of) Box 2, folders 82, 151, 167
Box 31 A, folder 92
Box 44, folder 12
Box 67, folder 35
Harlan, John M. (Letter from) Box 15, folder 92
Harpending, Asbury (Letters from) Box 11, folders 60, 119
Box 12, folders 3, 5, 8, 18, 20, 44, 48, 73, 104
Box 14, folder 16
Harpending, Asbury (Letters to) Box 47, folder 48
Box 49, folder 5 (2 letters)
Box 50, folders 1, 3
Harpending, Asbury (Mention of) Box 14, folders 4, 30
Harper, Alexander A. (Letter from) Box 1, folder A
Harris, Ira (1802-1875) (Mention of) Box 10, folder 22
Harris, Isham G. (Letter from) Box 12, folder 58
Harrison, Massilon (Mention of) Box 4, folder 13
Harrison, William H. (Mention of) Box 1, folder 2
Box 78, folder 89
Hart, Emanuel B. (Letters from) Box 20, folders 38, 47, 77, 120
Box 21, folders 52, 75
Hart, Emanuel B.(Letter to) Box 50, folders 1, 3 (2 letters)
Hartford Convention Box 78, folder 99
Hartsuff, George L. (Letters from) Box 8, folder 9
Box 69, folder 74
Hartsuff, George L.(Letters to) Box 46, folders 4, 21
Hartsuff, George L. (Mention of) Box 7, folder 52
Box 8, folder 36A
Box 30, folder 18A
Box 59, folder 31
Haskell, Dudley C. (Letter to) Box 52, folder 3
Hatchie Bridge, Tennessee (Engagement at, October 5, 1862) Box 7, folders 83-144
Hay, John M.(Letter to) Box 49, folder 2
Hay, John M. (Mention of) Box 10, folders 10, 22
Hayes, Rutherford B. (Letters from) Box 8, folder 158
Box 16, folder 147
Hayes, Rutherford B.(Letters to) Box 49, folder 6
Box 52, folder 2
Box 54, folder 40
Hayes, Rutherford B. (Mention of) Box 15, folder 12
Box 32, passim
Box 36, folder 50
Box 38, folder 103
Box 43, folder 53
Box 57, folders 26-27, 32, 35, 47, 50, 52, 54-55, 57, 84, 89
Box 62, folders 59, 61-62, 64, 66, 73, 107-108, 114
Box 66, folder 100
Box 68, folder 10
Box 76, folder 79
Box 88, folder 7
Hayes, Webb C. (Letter from) Box 32, folder 72
Hayes, Webb C. (Mention of) Box 66, folder 23
Healy, George P.A. (Letters from) Box 69, folders 15-16
Hecker, Isaac T. (Letters from) Box 31, folder 107
Hegeman family (Correspondence) Boxes 67-68
Box 76, folders 44-97
Box 78, folders 87-121
Hegeman family (Memorabilia) Box 107, folders 13-14
Hegeman, William (Correspondence) Box 49, folders 5 (6 letters), 6
Box 51, folders 3, 4
Box 67, folders 28-98
Box 76, folders 79-97
Hegeman, W.A. Ogden (Correspondence) Box 49, folder 6 (2 letters)
Box 50, folders 1 (4 letters), 2 (2 letters)
Box 52, folder 1
Box 68
Box 76, folder 78
Heintzelman, Samuel P. (Letters from) Box 10, folder 12
Box 16, folder 135
Box 17, folder 15A
Box 19, folder 165
Heintzelman, Samuel P.(Letters to) Box 50, folder 2 (2 letters)
Henderson, John B. (Letter from) Box 10, folder 150
Henry, Joseph (1797-1878) (Letter from) Box 15, folder 5
Hepburn, William P. (Letters from) Box 40, folder 60
Box 78, folder 26
Herron, Francis J. (Mention of) Box 53, folder 64
Hewit, Augustine F. (Letters from) Box 28, folder 114
Box 34, folder 113
Hewitt, Abram S. (Letter from) Box 33, folder 8
Hilgard, Julius E. (Manuscript by) Box 99, folder 13
Hill, Daniel H. (Mention of) Box 80, folder 25
Hill, Thomas (1818-1891) (Letters from) Box 69, folders 23, 105
Hindman, Thomas C. (Mention of) Box 7, folder 155
Hittell, John S. (Letter from) Box 15, folder 44
Hoff, Henry K. (Mention of) Box 11, folder 64
Hoffman, John T. (Letter from) Box 16, folder 155
Hoffman, John T. (Mention of) Box 68, folder 10
Hoffman, William (1807-1884) (Letter from) Box 8, folder 60